Guide to the New York University Archives Collection of the Heights Daily News RG.39.210
New York University Archives
New York University Archives Collection of the Heights Daily News
1933-1973
New York University Archives
Heights Daily News
RG.39.210
5.5 Linear Feet in 34 flat boxes and 18 microfilm reels
This collection contains issues from the student newspaper the Heights Daily Journal, dating from 1933 to 1973. This newspaper documented student life at NYU (particuarly at the University Heights campus in the Bronx), local and national news, campus living, and student clubs. NYU's University College of Arts and Science and the School of Engineering were located in the University Heights neighborhood of the Bronx from 1894 to 1973.
Historical Note
New York University has had many student newspapers since its founding. The University Heights campus and the Washington Square campus had separate student newspapers until 1973 when the University Heights campus closed.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains issues from the student newspaper the Heights Daily Journal, dating from 1933 to 1973. This newspaper documented student life at NYU (particuarly at the University Heights campus in the Bronx), local and national news, campus living, and student clubs. NYU's University College of Arts and Science and the School of Engineering were located in the University Heights neighborhood of the Bronx from 1894 to 1973.
Arrangement
Newspapers are arranged chronologically.
College student newspapers and periodicals.; Student activities.; Heights daily news (New York, N.Y.); New York University. University Heights; New York University. School of Engineering and Science; New York University -- Sports
- Microfilm Copies
  - Heights Daily News (2 copies), 1933-1935 (Box Shared University Archives 101, Reel 5011, Box Shared University Archives 103)
  - Heights Daily News (2 copies), 1935-1937 (Box Shared University Archives 101, Reel 5012, Box Shared University Archives 103)
  - Heights Daily News (2 copies), 1937-1939 (Box Shared University Archives 101, Reel 5013, Box Shared University Archives 103)
  - Heights Daily News (2 copies), 1939-1941 (Box Shared University Archives 101, Reel 5014, Box Shared University Archives 103)
  - Heights Daily News (2 copies), 1941-1944 (Box Shared University Archives 101, Reel 5015, Box Shared University Archives 103)
  - Heights Daily News (2 copies), 1944-1947 (Box Shared University Archives 101, Reel 5016, Box Shared University Archives 103)
  - Heights Daily News (2 copies), 1947-1949 (Box Shared University Archives 101, Reel 5017, Box Shared University Archives 103)
  - Heights Daily News (2 copies), 1949-1951 (Box Shared University Archives 101, Reel 5018, Box Shared University Archives 103)
  - Heights Daily News (2 copies), 1951-1953 (Box Shared University Archives 101, Reel 5019, Box Shared University Archives 103)
  - Heights Daily News (2 copies), 1953-1955 (Box Shared University Archives 101, Reel 5020, Box Shared University Archives 103)
  - Heights Daily News (2 copies), 1955-1957 (Box Shared University Archives 101, Reel 5021, Box Shared University Archives 103)
  - Heights Daily News (2 copies), 1957-1959 (Box Shared University Archives 101, Reel 5022, Box Shared University Archives 103)
  - Heights Daily News (2 copies), 1959-1961 (Box Shared University Archives 101, Reel 5023, Box Shared University Archives 103)
  - Heights Daily News (2 copies), 1961-1964 (Box Shared University Archives 101, Reel 5024, Box Shared University Archives 103)
  - Heights Daily News (2 copies), 1964-1967 (Box Shared University Archives 101, Reel 5025, Box Shared University Archives 103)
  - Heights Daily News (2 copies), 1967-1969 (Box Shared University Archives 101, Reel 5026, Box Shared University Archives 103)
  - Heights Daily News (2 copies), 1969-1972 (Box Shared University Archives 101, Reel 5027, Box Shared University Archives 103)
  - Heights Daily News (2 copies), 1972-1973 (Box Shared University Archives 101, Reel 5027a, Box Shared University Archives 103)